<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Rebelz Basketball</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Rebelz Basketball</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 19:22:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Drone Flight and FAA Part 107 Certification Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/stem/drone-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 19:22:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/stem/drone-flight/</guid>
      <description>What You&amp;rsquo;ll Learn FAA Regulations: Part 107 rules, airspace classifications, and legal requirements Drone Technology: Aircraft systems, sensors, cameras, and GPS navigation Flight Operations: Pre-flight planning, weather assessment, and safety protocols Aerial Photography/Videography: Camera operation, composition, and post-processing Data Collection: Mapping, surveying, and inspection techniques Emergency Procedures: Risk management and emergency response Business Applications: Commercial drone operations and career opportunities Drone Flight School &amp;amp; FAA Part 107 Certification Track&#xA;Through our Drone Flight School, participants are introduced to hands-on STEM learning with real-world applications.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>REBELZ Chess Collective</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/stem/chess/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jul 2025 19:21:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/stem/chess/</guid>
      <description>What You&amp;rsquo;ll Learn Chess Fundamentals: Piece movement, basic rules, and game notation Strategic Thinking: Pattern recognition, planning, and decision-making Tactical Combinations: Pins, forks, skewers, and discovered attacks Opening Principles: Development, center control, and king safety Endgame Techniques: Basic checkmate patterns and pawn promotion Game Analysis: Using chess engines and databases for improvement Tournament Play: Competition rules, time management, and sportsmanship The Rebelz Chess Collective is a strategy club designed to build mental discipline, patience, foresight, and emotional control.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>AI Assisted App Development</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/stem/ai-app-development/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/stem/ai-app-development/</guid>
      <description>What You&amp;rsquo;ll Learn AI Development Tools: Master popular AI-assisted coding platforms like GitHub Copilot, Cursor, and Claude Mobile App Development: Build native iOS and Android applications with AI assistance Web Development: Create responsive web applications using modern frameworks Machine Learning Integration: Implement AI features into your applications UI/UX Design: Design intuitive user interfaces with AI-powered design tools Project Management: Learn agile development methodologies and version control App Creation Lab – Build Your Own App</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Computer Science</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/stem/computer-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/stem/computer-science/</guid>
      <description>Computer Science Program Overview Our Computer Science program provides a comprehensive foundation in computational thinking, programming, and software development. Students will explore the fundamental concepts that power modern technology while developing practical skills for the digital age.&#xA;What You&amp;rsquo;ll Learn Programming Languages: Python, Java, JavaScript, C++, and more Data Structures &amp;amp; Algorithms: Arrays, linked lists, trees, sorting, searching Software Engineering: Design patterns, testing, debugging, and best practices Database Systems: SQL, NoSQL, database design and optimization Web Development: Front-end and back-end development Computer Networks: Internet protocols, security, and distributed systems Operating Systems: Process management, memory allocation, file systems Program Structure Foundation Level (Weeks 1-6) Introduction to programming with Python Basic data structures and algorithms Problem-solving methodologies Version control with Git Intermediate Level (Weeks 7-12) Object-oriented programming Advanced data structures Database design and SQL Web development fundamentals Advanced Level (Weeks 13-18) Software engineering principles System design concepts Advanced algorithms Capstone project development Core Subjects Programming Fundamentals Variables, functions, and control structures Object-oriented programming concepts Code organization and documentation Debugging and testing strategies Data Structures &amp;amp; Algorithms Arrays, stacks, queues, and linked lists Trees, graphs, and hash tables Sorting and searching algorithms Algorithm analysis and complexity Software Development Software development lifecycle Agile methodologies Code review and collaboration Project management tools Database Systems Relational database design SQL queries and optimization NoSQL databases Data modeling and normalization Prerequisites Strong mathematical foundation (Algebra II recommended) Logical thinking and problem-solving skills Basic computer literacy Commitment to continuous learning Tools and Technologies Programming Languages: Python, Java, JavaScript, C++, HTML/CSS Development Tools: Visual Studio Code, IntelliJ IDEA, Git, GitHub Databases: MySQL, PostgreSQL, MongoDB Frameworks: React, Node.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Summer Tournament Success</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/news/2023-07-15-summer-tournament-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 14:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/news/2023-07-15-summer-tournament-success/</guid>
      <description>Team Rebelz dominated the summer tournament, bringing home the championship trophy after an intense final game.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>About Rebelz Basketball Rebelz Basketball is an AAU program in the Philadelphia Circuit dedicated to developing young athletes both on and off the court. We focus on basketball fundamentals, teamwork, discipline, and character building.&#xA;Our program provides competitive basketball opportunities for talented youth, helping them reach their full potential while preparing them for success at the high school, collegiate, and beyond.&#xA;Our Mission To create a positive environment where young athletes can develop their basketball skills, build character, and learn valuable life lessons through competitive play.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ahnaf Mollah</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/ahnaf-mollah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/ahnaf-mollah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Amyr Mcclenton</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/amyr-mcclenton/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/amyr-mcclenton/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Charlie</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-charlie/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-charlie/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Deacon</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-deacon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-deacon/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach ICE</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-ice/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-ice/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Isaac</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-isaac/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-isaac/</guid>
      <description>Coach Isaac specializes in player development with a focus on guard skills and shooting technique. His training sessions emphasize fundamentals, basketball IQ, and game-situation drills.&#xA;Players under his guidance develop not only their basketball skills but also important life skills like time management, leadership, and resilience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Robel (RO)</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-robel-ro/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-robel-ro/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Coach Sah</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-sah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/coaches/coach-sah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gaoussou</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/gaoussou/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/gaoussou/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Haafiz Webb</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/haafiz-webb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/haafiz-webb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ian</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/ian/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/ian/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Jayden aka 30</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/jay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/jay/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>JB</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/jb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/jb/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kye</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/kye/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/kye/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lamont Harris</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/lamont-harris/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/lamont-harris/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Michael Chepyshev</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/michael-chepyshev/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/michael-chepyshev/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mohamed Konate</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/mohamed-konate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/mohamed-konate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Muhammad Asadullah</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/muhammad-asadullah/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/muhammad-asadullah/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Nate</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/nate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/nate/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robert Towns </title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/robert-towns/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/robert-towns/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ronald Coleman</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/ronald-coleman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/ronald-coleman/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sayid </title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/sayid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/sayid/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Shiheed Rice-Sloan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/shiheed-rice-sloan/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/shiheed-rice-sloan/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Support Rebelz Basketball</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/gofundme/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/gofundme/</guid>
      <description>Support Our Team We&amp;rsquo;re raising funds to support the Rebelz Basketball 18U AAU team in the Phila Circuit. Your contribution will help with:&#xA;Tournament fees Travel expenses Equipment and uniforms Training facilities Every donation makes a difference in these young athletes&amp;rsquo; lives!&#xA;Donate to Our Campaign</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team Registration</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/register/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/register/</guid>
      <description>Join Rebelz Basketball We&amp;rsquo;re currently accepting registrations for our AAU basketball teams in the Phila Circuit:&#xA;16U Team - For players born in 2008 17U Team - For players born in 2007 Registration Process Fill out the registration form below Attend a team tryout (dates will be provided after form submission) If selected, complete the payment process What We Offer Professional coaching Competitive tournament schedule Skills development College exposure opportunities Team gear and uniforms Join us and take your game to the next level!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Yasir P.</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/yasir-p/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/yasir-p/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zion Johnson</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/players/zion-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/players/zion-johnson/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
